Namaste sir, how are you doing?
Namaste ma'am, I am Harshant from
Jaipinagar.
We have heard about the facts of the
case.
We have been trying for just 2-3
months.
We have immediately responded to the
first meeting, created a WhatsApp
came to the boardroom, they have
created an open house.
I am Harish sir, he is the chairman.
He has been working for a long time.
All that is a big deal.
This open house is attended by
everyone.
Everyone is in the common man, in
the other background,
sitting together in the boardroom,
talking to everyone,
asking about the case, to the
officials,
to the officials who are involved in
the zone,
to make this kind of direction.
It is very good.
We are very happy as citizens.
So what I am telling you is,
this is the grievance related to the
BDX.
Just contact me on WhatsApp.
I will send messages on WhatsApp.
They have created a token system.
It is a very good initiative.
Everything is getting streamed live
on YouTube.
So, if people are sitting together,
watching YouTube videos,
if they are doing so much,
they will solve the problem.
Thank you very much.